totokaelo.com 2018-08-29

# Totokaelo Privacy Policy

###### PRIVACY POLICY

Effective Date: November 04, 2017 

PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. By using WWW.TOTOKAELO.COM or any other site owned or operated by Totokaelo, LLC (“TOTOKAELO”) in the future, you are deemed to have agreed to this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”). This Privacy Policy is a part of the Terms of Service for this website (“Site”) and elaborates how TOTOKAELO will protect your personal information as well as your choices concerning TOTOKAELO’s use of your personal information. We may change this policy from time to time in order to address new issues and reflect changes on the Site. We will post those changes here so please refer back to this policy regularly.

###### INFORMATION COLLECTED ABOUT YOU

Email addresses and other personally identifiable information, such as first and last name, home or other physical address, telephone number, and other such information are collected only when voluntarily provided by a visitor to the Site.

###### Information Collection

  * By Browsing. As you browse the Site, it collects log file, Internet protocol (IP) addresses of your computer, “cookies”1 (described below), web beacons, and other standard tracking data TOTOKAELO uses to evaluate Site traffic and usage patterns. Such information is aggregated with tracking data from all Site visitors.
  * By Site Requirement. Some portions of the Site may require you to give TOTOKAELO personally identifiable information such as your name, address, email address, transaction information, and/or other information by which TOTOKAELO may contact you.
  * By User’s Voluntary Submission. If you communicate with TOTOKAELO by email, or otherwise complete online forms, registrations, or surveys, any information provided in such communications may be collected as personal information.

We collect personal information from you only if you voluntarily give it to us. The information we collect includes your name, email address, postal address, and credit card numbers when you place an order, save your information with us, or when you participate in a sweepstakes or promotion. TOTOKAELO may use your personal information collected online to process and fulfill an order. TOTOKAELO also collects email addresses at various locations within the Site including when you order from the Site so that we may send you any necessary email messages related to your order. We may contact you with marketing and promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. If at any time you decide that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of TOTOKAELO’s communications, or contact us at hello@totokaelo.com. We also maintain a record of your product interests, purchases and other information that might enable us to enhance and personalize your shopping experience.

###### YOUR RIGHT TO CHOOSE

Any personal information that TOTOKAELO collects from you through the Site is information that you specifically and voluntarily provide. You may choose not to provide any or all of the information that is requested through the Site. By so choosing, you may limit your ability to use the Site. In the event that you no longer want us to process or utilize your personal information, please contact us using the “Contact Us” form on the Site or inform us of this choice at hello@totokaelo.com.

###### USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

You do not have to share any personal information (like full name, e-mail address, home address, telephone number, etc.) to view the Site. The information collected by and through the Site is owned solely by TOTOKAELO. The information collected by and through the Site will be used solely by TOTOKAELO, its affiliated corporations, or other entities that are involved in the operation of this Site for TOTOKAELO’s internal purposes. TOTOKAELO may use the information collected and provided, individually or in an aggregate form, including but not limited to, for the following:

  * to personalize the Site according to your preferences based on the aggregated information;
  * to evaluate products and services TOTOKAELO may offer to you;
  * to deliver a product or service you requested, or to confirm or fulfill an order or request you have made;
  * to contact you about the Site;
  * to monitor or improve the use of the Site;
  * to customize the advertising and content you see;
  * to monitor compliance with the Terms of Use for the Site;
  * to provide special offers to you from TOTOKAELO and/or its affiliates and other third parties; and to send you promotional material on behalf of TOTOKAELO and/or its affiliates and other third parties.

We may also collect information from you offline, such as when you participate in a sweepstakes or contest, or make a purchase at a store. We may obtain customer lists, demographic and other information about you from commercial sources.

TOTOKAELO also uses technology to collect certain information automatically, like your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address (which is the automatic number assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider when you surf the Web, or unique device identifier (“UDID”), international mobile equipment identity (“IMEI”), mobile equipment identifier (“MEID”) or media access control “MAC”) address; computer operating system (e.g., Microsoft Windows, Mac OS); your browser (e.g., Internet Explorer, Firefox); websites visited before or after you visit the Site; pages viewed and activities at the Site; and advertisements shown or clicked on.

To improve TOTOKAELO’s performance, we may combine personal information you provide us online and in our store.

###### SHARING YOUR INFORMATION

With Whom Information is Shared At times, TOTOKAELO may share your personally identifiable information with others for various purposes. The following outlines the ways in which your information may be shared with others:

Agents: TOTOKAELO may employ other businesses, certain services, and individuals to perform functions on TOTOKAELO’s behalf. A non-exhaustive list of examples includes fulfilling orders, sending e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, Site analysis, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing payments, and providing customer service. These agents may have access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. In an effort to protect you, these agents who have access to personally identifiable information either (a) must operate and use your personally identifiable information in a manner consistent with the current Privacy Policy, or (b) are subject to contractual obligations to maintain such information as confidential subject to certain exceptions. However, TOTOKAELO is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other companies.

Aggregate Information: TOTOKAELO may share aggregate information such as demographics and Site usage statistics to other organizations. When this type of information is shared, the other parties do not have access to your personally identifiable information.

Opt-in and Opt-out Programs: Throughout the Site you may be presented with opportunities to receive mailings from third parties or TOTOKAELO. An opt-in/opt-out message may ask you if you would like your information to be shared. If you do choose to have your information shared, please be aware that TOTOKAELO is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other companies, and you should review the privacy practices of such companies prior to providing your personally identifiable information. If you would not like your information to be shared with third parties, or if you would like to stop receiving mailings from third parties or TOTOKAELO, you may send an opt-out message in an email to TOTOKAELO at hello@totokaelo.com.

Third-Party Traffic Measurement Services: The Site may use a third party to conduct traffic measurement services to analyze the traffic on the Site. Audience and traffic measurement services allow TOTOKAELO to collect anonymous traffic and behavior information from the Site by monitoring anonymous visitor activity. The traffic measurement services may themselves set and access their own cookies on your computer if you choose to have your cookies enabled in your browser. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.

TOTOKAELO Affiliates: TOTOKAELO may share your information (including, without limitation, personally identifiable information) with affiliates of TOTOKAELO.

Business Transfers: The Site, TOTOKAELO and/or an affiliate or division of TOTOKAELO may be sold along with its assets, or other transactions may occur in which your personally identifiable information is one of the business assets transferred. In such a case, your personally identifiable information, which TOTOKAELO has gathered, may be one of the business assets TOTOKAELO transfers.

Legal Process: In the event TOTOKAELO is required to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process your personally identifiable information may be disclosed pursuant to such subpoena, court order, or legal process, which may be without notice to you.

###### THE SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION

We strive to protect the privacy of your information during order transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer software, which encrypts order information you transmit. While we implement these and other security measures on the Site, unfortunately no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Thus, although we endeavor to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of the information that you submit to us via the Site and you do so at your own risk. Since the Internet is a worldwide environment, you acknowledge and agree that your personal information may be transferred to other countries. You play a role in protecting your information as well. Because your password permits access to personal information, please keep your password secret and do not disclose it to others.

###### COOKIES

TOTOKAELO may store certain information on your computer in the form of a “cookie” or similar file. These files enable us to tailor the Site to reflect your listed or historical preferences. Most web browsers allow web users to exercise control over such files on their computers by erasing them, blocking them, or notifying the user when such a file is stored. Please refer to your browser’s instructions to learn about these functions. Please note that if you disable or delete these files you may not have access to certain features and services that make your online experience more efficient and enjoyable. These and other technologies also allow delivery of advertising that directly relates to offers that may be of interest to you. If, however, you prefer not to receive relevant banner advertisements, you may opt out any time by emailing hello@totokaelo.com.

TOTOKAELO uses other methods of automatic collection to determine information about visitors to the Site, including your computer’s Internet Protocol address, browser type, or the webpage you were visiting before you came to the Site, pages of the Site that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Site, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to provide better customer services, enhance our product offerings, and detect potential misuse or fraud.

###### NO LIABILITY FOR ACTS OF THIRD PARTIES

We have no liability for disclosure of information due to errors in transmission to third parties or unauthorized acts of third parties.

###### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. From time to time, we may review and revise this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time and notify you by publishing an updated version of the Privacy Policy on the Site. Your continued use of the Site after any such changes constitutes your acceptance of the new terms.

###### CHILDREN

The Children’s Online Privacy Act imposes certain requirements on websites directed at children under 13 that collect information on those children and on websites that knowingly collect information from children under 13. The Site is not directed to children under 13 and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 13.

###### JURISDICTION

You acknowledge and agree that regardless of your physical location or the location of any server on which your information may be accessed or used that this Privacy Policy and the laws of the United States of America shall govern and control the privacy issues related to this Site.

###### YOUR QUESTIONS AND COMMENTS

We invite you to learn more about us. Please contact us at hello@totokaelo.com.
